RG 097, Connecticut Commission on the Arts
Connecticut State Library
- Series 12. News Clippings, 1962-1978
  - North Branford's Selectmen's meeting, 1966 September (Box 60)
  - Letter to the (Courant) Editor Re Commission, 1966 September (Box 60)
  - O"Neill Foundatin Panel, 1966 August (Box 60)
  - George Sweetman's statement Re Commission, 1966 October (Box 60)
  - New Hampshire Arts Conference, 1966 October (Box 60)
  - New England Research Center - Brian Klitz, 1966 October (Box 60)
  - Franchetti Opera, "As a Conductor Dreams', 1955 October-November (Box 60)
  - Torrington Forum, 1966 December - 1967 January (Box 60)
  - Commission moves to new quarters, 1966 December (Box 60)
  - Thomaston Opera House and Arts Council, 1966 October (Box 60)
  - Commission selected for National Consultant Service, 1966 October-November (Box 60)
  - Architect selection legislation, 1966 October - 1967 February (Box 60)
  - Commission publishes calendar, 1966 October (Box 60)
  - Windsor-Hartford Symphony Auxiliary meeting, 1966 October (Box 60)
  - Willimantic Rotary Club meeting, 1966 October (Box 60)
  - Greenwich Junior League Symposium, 1966 October-November (Box 60)
  - Formation of Commission, 1965-1968 (Box 60)
  - Arts Commission personnel speaking engagements, 1966-1969 (Box 60)
  - Temporary Commission on Arts, 1962-1965 (Box 60)
  - News clips, 1969 (Box 61)
  - News clips, 1969-1971 (Box 61)
  - News clips - Political appointments, 1969-1971 (Box 61)
  - Grants, 1969-1970 (Box 61)
  - SPRED (School Progress Reaches Each District), 1969-1970 (Box 61)
  - Bradley Display, 1969-1970 (Box 61)
  - Visiting artist, 1969 (Box 61)
  - News clippings, 1969 (Box 61)
  - News clippings, 1968-1970 (Box 61)
  - Music clippings, 1968-1970 (Box 61)
  - Theater - film clippings, 1968-1970 (Box 61)
  - Commission sponsored dance programs, 1968-1969 (Box 61)
  - News clips, 1968 (Box 61)
  - News clips, 1968 (Box 61)
  - Visual arts - clippings, 1968-1970 (Box 61)
  - Poetry, 1968 (Box 61)
  - Architecture, 1968-1970 (Box 61)
  - Visiting artist program - Artists-in-residence, 1968-1970 (Box 61)
  - Association of Community Theaters, 1968-1969 (Box 61)
  - Dance, 1968-1969 (Box 61)
  - Theater for Children, 1968-1969 (Box 61)
  - Calendar of events, "Lively Arts', 1968 (Box 61)
  - Selected Times clippings, 1968 May (Box 61)
  - Photography, 1968 (Box 61)
  - Theater in the street, 1968 (Box 61)
  - Film programs, 1968 (Box 61)
  - Revitalization Corps, 1968 (Box 61)
  - Anderson, Mis Marian (Box 61)
  - Basile, John C. R. Dr. (Box 61)
  - Chubb, Thomas C. (Box 61)
  - Cohen, Herbert L. (Box 61)
  - Donnell, Hugh (Box 61)
  - Eisner, Mrs. Anita (Box 61)
  - Kappel, Philip (Box 61)
  - Keller, Anthony S. (Box 61)
  - Malkan, Mrs. Joan Brainerd (Box 61)
  - Mayhew, Edgar De N. (Box 61)
  - Metcalfe, Catherine (Box 61)
  - Mitnick, Paul (Box 61)
  - Morency, Paul W. (Box 61)
  - Redlich, Mrs. Herta Glaz (Box 61)
  - Reed, Joseph Verner (Box 61)
  - Ribicoff, Mrs. Irving S. (Belle) (Box 61)
  - Rosenstein, Samuel N. (Box 61)
  - Wolf, Mrs. Mary Hunter (Box 61)
  - Van Doren, Mark (Box 61)
  - Project Create, 1967-1969 (Box 61)
  - Project Create, 1967-1969 (Box 61)
  - News clips, 1972 (Box 62)
  - Grant clips, 1971-1972 (Box 62)
  - VAP clips, 1971-1972 (Box 62)
  - Visiting Artists Program, Visiting Poets Program, 1971 (Box 62)
  - Legislators' support of arts, 1971 (Box 62)
  - Legislative hearings - Bills supporting arts programs, 1971 (Box 62)
  - Miscellaneous clips, 1971 (Box 62)
  - 300 years of Connecticut architecture, 1971 (Box 62)
  - Dance clips, 1971 (Box 62)
  - Music clips, 1971 (Box 62)
  - Theater clips, 1971 (Box 62)
  - State song search, 1971 (Box 62)
  - Commission meeting at New Britain Museum, 1971 July (Box 62)
  - Miscellaneous arts news Re: Artists, commissioners, etc., 1971 (Box 62)
  - Feature articles, Mary Hunter Wolf, Anthony Keller, 1971 (Box 62)
  - Clippings - Concerts at the Capitol Series, 1971 (Box 62)
  - Michael Croman: Union Station hearing, New London CDAP meeting, Groton, 1971 (Box 62)
  - Arts - Recreation Conference, 1971 May (Box 62)
  - Summer arts program grants, 1971 (Box 62)
  - Title III applications and proposals (Box 62)
  - American Dance Festival, 1971 (Box 62)
  - Grants to community arts organizations, 1971 (Box 62)
  - Dance workshops, General dance news, 1971 (Box 62)
  - Ballet grants, 1971 (Box 62)
  - Community arts councils, 1971 (Box 62)
  - News clippings, 1971 (Box 62)
  - News clips, 1970 (Box 62)
  - News clips, 1970 (Box 62)
  - News clippings, 1970 (Box 62)
  - Berkman - Parker, etc., 1969-1971 (Box 62)
  - News clips, 1969 (Box 62)
  - News clips, 1969 (Box 62)
  - News clips, 1974 December (Box 63)
  - News clips, 1974 November (Box 63)
  - News clips, 1974 October (Box 63)
  - News clips, 1974 September (Box 63)
  - News clips, 1974 August (Box 63)
  - News clips, 1974 July (Box 63)
  - News clips, 1974 June (Box 63)
  - News clips, 1974 May (Box 63)
  - News clips, 1974 April (Box 63)
  - News clips, 1974 March-April (Box 63)
  - News clips, 1974 March (Box 63)
  - News clips, 1974 February (Box 63)
  - News clips, 1974 January (Box 63)
  - News clips - Funds, 1973 (Box 63)
  - News clips, 1973 December (Box 63)
  - News clips, 1973 November (Box 63)
  - News clips, 1973 October (Box 63)
  - News clips, 1973 September (Box 63)
  - News clips, 1973 August (Box 63)
  - News clips, 1973 July (Box 63)
  - News clips, 1973 June (Box 63)
  - News clips, 1973 May (Box 63)
  - News clips, 1973 April (Box 63)
  - News clips, 1973 March (Box 63)
  - News clips, 1973 February (Box 63)
  - News clips, 1973 January (Box 63)
  - News clips, 1972 October-December (Box 63)
  - News clips, 1972 (Box 63)
  - News clips, 1972 (Box 63)
  - News clips, 1972 (Box 63)
  - Contours II Fiscal 1978, Sponsor references (Box 64)
  - Contours II Fiscal 1978, performance group notification letter (Box 64)
  - News clips, 1976 September (Box 64)
  - News clips, 1976 August (Box 64)
  - News clips, 1976 July (Box 64)
  - News clips, 1976 June (Box 64)
  - News clips, 1976 May (Box 64)
  - News clips, 1976 April (Box 64)
  - News clips, 1976 March (Box 64)
  - News clips, 1976 February (Box 64)
  - News clips, 1976 January (Box 64)
  - News clips, 1975 December (Box 64)
  - News clips, 1975 November (Box 64)
  - News clips, 1975 October (Box 64)
  - News clips, 1975 September (Box 64)
  - News clips, 1975 August (Box 64)
  - News clips, 1975 July (Box 64)
  - News clips, 1975 June (Box 64)
  - News clips, 1975 May (Box 64)
  - News clips, 1975 April (Box 64)
  - News clips, 1975 March (Box 64)
  - News clips, 1975 February (Box 64)
  - News clips, 1975 June (Box 64)
  - Miscellaneous, 1975 (Box 65)
  - General Agency, 1975 (Box 65)
  - Bloomfield, 1975 (Box 65)
  - Bridgeport, 1975 (Box 65)
  - Corrections, 1975 (Box 65)
  - Hartford, 1975 (Box 65)
  - Litchfield, 1975 (Box 65)
  - Lower Fairfield, 1975 (Box 65)
  - Meriden, 1975 (Box 65)
  - Middletown, 1975-1976 (Box 65)
  - Naugatuck Valley, 1975 (Box 65)
  - New Haven, 1975 (Box 65)
  - New London, 1975 (Box 65)
  - Norwich, 1975 (Box 65)
  - Norwalk, 1975 (Box 65)
  - Suffield, 1974-1975 (Box 65)
  - Waterbury, 1974-1975 (Box 65)
  - Visual Arts Collaborative, 1975-1976 (Box 65)
  - Connecticut Public Arts Employment Administration, 1976 (Box 65)
  - Features, 1975 (Box 65)
  - Shakespeare - Atheneum Cutback in Services, 1976 (Box 65)
  - News clippings, 1976 October (Box 65)
  - News clippings, 1977 November (Box 65)
  - News clippings, 1976 November (Box 65)
  - News clippings, 1977 January (Box 65)
  - News clippings, 1977 January (Box 65)
  - News clippings, 1977 February (Box 65)
  - News clippings, 1977 March (Box 65)
  - News clippings, 1977 April (Box 65)
  - News clippings, 1977 May (Box 65)
  - News clippings, 1977 June (Box 65)
  - News clippings, 1977 July (Box 65)
  - News clippings, 1977 August (Box 65)
  - News clippings, 1977 September (Box 65)
  - News clippings, 1977 October (Box 65)
  - News clippings, 1977 December (Box 65)
  - News clippings, 1978 January (Box 65)
  - News clippings, 1978 February (Box 65)
  - News clippings, 1978 March (Box 65)
  - Applications For Community Development Sunday Pictorial, 1971 January 24 (Box 65)
  - The New Haven Register - 7 Copies (Box 65)
</ead